原創翻譯  雙語字幕
最新連載海外影視劇下載
請登陸 www.YYeTs.com
僅供交流學習  禁止商用盈利
翻譯     克里斯   杏仁斯嘉麗   joy_bwl
翻譯     肉松   euniceluo   白月   楊愛菜
時間軸     念念   今   壬虛浪影
校對     喃喃
后期     8T
總監     喃喃
*我遇到些麻煩  但很快就會解決*
*I got some troubles, but they won't last*
*我要躺在草地上*
*I'm gonna lay right down here in the grass*
*煩惱很快就會煙消云散*
*And pretty soon, all my troubles will pass*
*因為我在...*
*'cause I'm in shoo-shoo-shoo, shoo-shoo-shoo*
*愜意美好的糖果鎮*
*shoo-shoo, shoo-shoo, shoo-shoo, Sugar Town*
*我養的狗從不跟我親近*
*I never had a dog that liked me some*
*也沒想過要交什么朋友*
*Never had a friend or wanted one*
*我就躺下  對太陽大笑*
*So I just lay back and laugh at the sun*
*因為我在...*
*'cause I'm in shoo-shoo-shoo, shoo-shoo-shoo*
*愜意美好的糖果鎮*
*shoo-shoo, shoo-shoo, shoo-shoo, Sugar Town*
辛那邦
吉恩
*昨天田納西下起了雨*
*Yesterday, it rained in Tennessee*
*塔拉哈西也陰雨連綿*
*I heard it also rained in Tallahassee*
*但我一點也沒被淋濕*
*But not a drop fell on little old me*
*因為我在...*
*'cause I was in shoo-shoo-shoo, shoo-shoo-shoo*
*愜意美好的糖果鎮*
*shoo-shoo, shoo-shoo, shoo-shoo, Sugar Town*
*如果我家纏萬貫*
*If I had a million dollars or ten*
*我會把錢送給世人*
*I'd give it to ya, world, and then*
*你們就會讓我獨自享受*
*you'd go away and let me spend*
*糖果鎮的好時光*
*my life in shoo-shoo-shoo, shoo-shoo-shoo*
*愜意美好的糖果鎮*
*shoo-shoo, shoo-shoo, shoo-shoo, Sugar Town*
他們正前往文頓街和第二十大街路口...
They're coming up on Vinton and 20th now...
去看看那邊
Check over that way, would you?
-好的  -前往附近的回收廠
‭- Will do. - ...heading over to salvage and recycling.
收到  五分鐘后到
Copy that. I'm about 5 out.
你看沒看到有個穿燈芯絨大衣的人
You see a guy in a corduroy coat go by?
先生
Sir?
Sir.
年紀不大  深色頭發  燈芯絨大衣
Young guy, dark hair, corduroy coat.
奧馬哈警局巡警
怎么說
How about it?
尼克  過來一下
Hey, Nick. Come here.
想出來嗎
Wanna come on out here?
把你的外套敞開
Go ahead and open your jacket for me.
我現在要逮捕你  先生
I'm placing you under arrest, sir.
請把雙手舉過頭頂
Put your hands on your head, please.
尼克  能幫我拿一下嗎
Nick, you want to grab those for me?
沒問題
You got it.
好了  我們走
All right, let's go.
干得好
Nice job.
什么都別說  明白嗎  找個律師
Say nothing, you understand?! Get a lawyer!
找個律師
Get a lawyer.
混蛋
Asshole.
女士們
Ladies.
吉恩
Hey, Gene.
午餐吃得還行吧
Nice lunch?
是啊  你需要什么
Oh, yeah. Whatcha need?
面包卷快好了
Rolls about to come out.
沒問題
You got it.
絕命律師
第三季 第一集
我能不能告訴霍華德
So, can I, uh, tell Howard
你不辭職也不退休了
you're not quitting or retiring or whatever?
還有  能不能把這些破玩意從墻上弄下來
And can we take all this shit down off the walls?
我這就打給霍華德
I'm gonna go call Howard.
吉米
Jimmy.
你剛剛承認犯了一項重罪你知道吧
You do realize ‭you just confessed to a felony?
算是吧
I guess.
可你覺得好多了  不是嗎
But you feel better, right?
再說了  就我們倆  空口無憑
Besides, ‭it's your word against mine.
當然
Absolutely.
他要回去
Coming back.
我說了什么有什么關系呢  霍華德
What's it matter what I said, Howard?
你何必要拒絕一番好意呢
Why you lookin' a gift horse in the mouth?
他只是...
He just --
對  不管怎樣  他現在已經釋懷了
Yeah, well, whatever it was, he's over it now, all right?
順便說一句  不客氣
And by the way, you're welcome.
霍華德又活過來了
Well, Howard's breathing again.
你讓他很高興
You made him very happy.
吉米
Jimmy!
吉米  如果你想幫忙
Jimmy, if you're gonna help,
至少講究點技巧  好嗎
a-at least use a little finesse, would you?
"技巧"  你怎么...
"Finesse"? Whaddya...
別亂扯了
Would -- Quit yanking at it.
你把胡桃木上的漆面
You're -- You're pulling the varnish
都扯下來了
right off the walnut.
我才沒扯掉漆面呢
Not pullin' any varnish off the walnut.
當然有了  你看  看見了嗎
You most certainly are. Look. Look! See?
也許你在用膠帶把它們粘住之前
Well, maybe you shoulda thought about the friggin' walnut
就應該想到那破核桃木的
before you covered it in duct tape.
我不需要你幫忙
I don't need your help!
我壓根都沒要你幫忙
I don't recall ever asking for it.
抱歉  行了吧
I'm sorry, okay?
用技巧  好吧  給我做個示范
Finesse, fine. Show me. Demonstrate.
像這樣
Like this.
溫柔地
Gently...
拇指把它卷起來
...roll it with your thumbs.
左邊  然后右邊
Left, and then right.
看
See?
拇指上下交替
Alternate the thumbs, up and down.
好好卷  用力卷
Get a nice, tight roll going.
查克  我覺得你才需要被好好"卷"一下
Chuck, I think you're the one that needs a nice, tight roll.
來吧  試著做做看
Come on. Show me.
溫柔地
Gently.
溫柔點
Gently. ‭
左邊  然后右邊
Left, then right.
左  右
Left, right.
我懂了  "反復打蠟"
I get it. Wax on, wax off.
宮城先生
Mr. Miyagi.
出自《龍威小子》
"Karate Kid."
沒懂嗎
Seriously?
天啊
Oh, my God.
《梅寶大冒險》
"The Adventures of Mabel."
我從來都沒想起過這本書
I-I haven't thought about this in forever.
你記得這本嗎  查克
You remember this, Chuck?
記得
I do.
-哈里·瑟斯頓·佩科寫的  -是啊
- Harry Thurston Peck. - ‭Yeah!
梅寶進了山
Mabel goes into the mountain,
她遇到了棕精靈國王
and she meets the King of the Brownies,
他給了她
and he gives her...
一種特別好吃的果凍  然后
some kind of ‭super delicious jelly and...
天啊  1912年
Holy crap. 1912.
是啊  這本是達文波特奶奶的
Yeah. Belonged to Grammie Davenport.
她在書上寫了名字
She wrote her name in it.
泰坦尼克號沉沒那年
She was reading that to her schoolkids
她給學生們讀過
the year the Titanic went down.
厲害
Damn.
媽媽又給我讀
And Mom read it to me.
我給你讀的
I read it to you.
你不記得了
You don't remember.
記得
Yeah, yeah.
你一說我現在想起來了
I do, now that you say it.
記得
Yeah.
我當時多大  五六歲
What was I -- like 5 or 6?
你曾經對一盞奇怪的夜燈特別癡迷
You had this weird night-light that you were so crazy about.
它是...
It was, um...
是達菲鴨
It was Daffy Duck!
長著奇怪的紅喙的達菲鴨
It was some Daffy Duck rip-off with this weird red bill.
-鳥嘴  對  喙  -對對對
- Mouth. Oh, yeah, yeah, the bill. - ‭Yeah. ‭Yeah, yeah, yeah.
它經常會特別燙
And it used to get so hot,
我們以為它會把房子燒著了  但是
we thought it would burn the house down, but --
-對  -你誰都不讓碰
- Right. - ...you wouldn't let anybody touch it.
是啊  那真是  你記性真好  查克
Yeah, that's a -- ‭You got a great memory, Chuck.
紅喙什么的
That red bill and everything.
那個住在我們家前面三棟房子的
What was the name of that little girl that lived, uh,
女孩叫什么來著
three houses up from us?
-她當時留著娃娃頭  -吉米
- She had, like, a pageboy haircut. ‭- Jimmy.
她總是臟兮兮的  一直都好臟
And she was always in the dirt, always dirty.
-吉米  -我喜歡她
- Jimmy! - ‭I liked her.
-她總是  -吉米
- She was always -- ‭- Jimmy.
別以為我會忘記今天在這發生的事
Don't think I'll ever forget what happened here today.
你會付出代價的
And you will pay.
你沒提到我的花園
You didn't mention my garden.
花園是你后院的一部分
Well, your garden is part of your backyard,
所以它自動算在給珍的財產里
so it's automatically included in the property that goes to Jenn.
它和房子是一起的  媽媽
It comes with the house, Mom.
我覺得你得特別提一下
Well, I think you need to mention it by name
萬一某些壞法官耍陰招就不好辦了
in case some dirty judge decides to play tricks.
好  可以的
Okay, we can do that.
花園
Let's see. Garden.
我回來了  女士們你們好
Hey, I'm back. Oh, hi, ladies.
吉米·麥吉爾
Jimmy McGill.
吉米  我們快結束了
Hey, Jimmy. We are almost done here.
真棒  我能
Great. Can I, uh...
我們快結束了
We're almost done.
我一會兒找你
I'll be with you in a minute.
還要提到我的蓮花池
And mention my lily pond.
在我的花園里
It's in my garden.
蓮花池
Lily pond.
好了  女士們
‭Okay, ladies.
非常感謝你的幫助
Thanks so much for your help.
您太客氣了
Oh, you're very welcome.
謝謝你們兩位的耐心
Thank you both for being so patient.
阿亨夫人  如果您或瑪格麗特
And, Mrs. Aherne, if you or Margaret
還有什么需要  任何需要
ever need anything from me -- anything at all --
隨時給我打電話
you can call me day or night.
這是蘇馬克斯夫人和她的女兒珍
This is Mrs. Siemasko and her daughter Jenn.
對不起  我有點糊涂了
I'm sorry. I got my wires crossed a little.
再見
Uh... ‭Bye.
-再見  -一路平安
- Bye. - Drive safe.
-謝謝  -謝謝你們
- Thank you. - Okay, thank you.
你是我的超級英雄
You are a superhero.
我欠你太多
I owe you big-time.
查克怎么樣
So, how's Chuck?
危機解除了...
Crisis averted...
我想是的
I guess.
他又變回了以前的查克  所以...
I mean, he's back to being the same old Chuck, so...
想說說嗎
Wanna talk about it?
看情況
Depends.
有可能會涉及那件
It may or may not involve
你說你決不想討論的事
that thing you said you never, ever wanted to discuss.
那好吧  謝謝
Okay, then, thanks.
我得回去干活了
I gotta get back to it.
不如我們今天休息吧
How 'bout we call it a day?
我請你吃晚飯
I'll buy you some dinner.
你開玩笑吧
You're kidding, right?
你知道我的工作落后了多少嗎
You realize how far behind I am?
更別提我現在還有八個遺囑需要處理
Not to mention now I've got eight entire wills to finish up.
你說什么  遺囑的工作我來做
Whaddya talking about? I'll do the wills.
-不用你做  -我當然要做
- No, you won't. ‭- 'Course I will.
做遺囑  他們是我的委托人
Do the wills. They're my clients.
他們是我的委托人
They're my clients.
我們不是合伙人  記得嗎
You and I aren't partners, remember?
一旦我接手了這些人
Once I take these people on,
-就不能再把他們還給你  -得了吧
- I can't just reassign them to you. - ‭Aw, c'mon.
你這么較真干什么
Why you getting all, like, legal on me, huh?
誰會在意
Who cares?
我跟每個委托人都說了
Look, I told every single one of them the situation --
只有我在  你今天不在
that they'd be getting me instead of you.
我勸他們改天再來找你
I tried to talk them all into coming back another day.
六個人離開了  也許你可以把這些人追回來
Six of 'em left. ‭Maybe you'll get those back.
如果這是錢的問題  我...
I mean, look, if this is about the money, I have --
不是錢的問題  錢你留著好了
It's not about the money. You can keep the money.
別以為我想這樣
Don't act like I wanted this.
天哪  好像我在吃鍋望盆似的
Jesus, like I need more on my plate.
你生氣了嗎
Are you mad?
我沒生氣
I'm not mad.
我只是...
I'm just, uh...
在想些事情
...thinking about things.
今天有那么一會兒  查克沒有討厭我
For 10 minutes today, Chuck didn't hate me.
我都忘了那是什么感覺了
I forgot what that felt like.
吉米
Jimmy.
你剛剛承認犯了一項重罪你知道吧
You do realize ‭you just confessed to a felony?
算是吧
I guess.
可你覺得好多了  是吧
But you feel better, right?
再說了  就我們倆  空口無憑
Besides, ‭it's your word against mine.
到這里就結束了
That's the end of it.
霍華德
Howard?
下面沒有了
That's the end. ‭
你能...
Could you...?
好的
Oh, yeah.
你現在相信我了嗎
Well, now do you believe me?
我都不知道該從何說起
I don't even know where to begin.
但是  是的  我相信你
But yes, I believe you.
你弟弟是一個超級大混蛋
Your brother is one ‭world-class son of a bitch.
別見怪
No offense.
不過我真希望你在錄音之前
I just -- I really wish you'd told me
能先把計劃告訴我
about these plans of yours before you went out and did it.
我知道  霍華德  我很后悔誤導了你
I know, Howard, ‭and I regret misleading you.
只是我必須得掌握一些真憑實據
It's just that a certain... vérité had to be established.
我不是說你差點把我嚇出心臟病的事
I'm not talking about the heart attack that you nearly gave me.
查克  這卷錄音帶...
Chuck, this tape --
我不確定這帶子有什么用
I'm not sure ‭exactly what it accomplishes.
你比我更懂證據法規
Look, you know evidentiary rules better than I do,
一盤秘密錄制的帶子
but a secretly recorded tape
和有疑問的證據鏈
with a problematic chain of evidence?
你很難讓這些證據上庭
You're gonna have a helluva time getting that admitted.
沒錯
I agree.
就算你想辦法把證據呈給陪審團
And if you somehow put it in front of a jury,
吉米會叫一批音頻專家
Jimmy'd call a dozen audio experts,
說那不是他的聲音
say that voice isn't his,
說那盤帶子被處理過
say the -- the tape had been edited.
他確實會
He would, indeed.
你是為了梅薩維德的凱文·沃弛泰爾才演這出嗎
Are you thinking about playing this for Kevin Wachtell at Mesa Verde?
雖然我很想留住他們
Because as much as I would love to,
但生意已經黃了
that ship has sailed.
我們無論如何也找不回他們了
We're never getting them back, regardless.
我覺得我們連那里的門都進不去
Oh, I doubt we could even get in the door over there.
查克  如果那盤帶子在法庭上沒用
Chuck, if that tape is useless in a court of law
也沒有公眾輿論的支持
and no help ‭in the court of public opinion,
還有什么意義
what's the point?
我想不到有什么用途
Because I can't think of a single use for it.
我可以
I can.
別這么做
5J汽車配件
自助服務  工具租借
先生  我們十五分鐘后打烊
Hey, mister, ‭we're closin' in 15 minutes.
幫我叫輛出租車  行嗎
Call me a cab, will ya?
那你的車呢
What about your vehicle?
送你了
Keep it.
狩獵恐怖分子許可證
5J汽車回收廠
Five J's auto salvage.
百老匯街  波比·福斯特的店
Broadway, uh, ‭at -- at Bobby Foster's.
小心暴力混蛋
是  厄  厄什么來著
Yeah, Ehr-- Ehr-- Ehr-- How is it again?
厄門紹特
Ehrmantraut.
是  厄門紹特
Yeah, Ehrmantraut.
是
Yeah.
讓他到了停在門口按喇叭
Just tell him ‭to pull up to the gate and honk.
行  好  謝謝
Okay, yeah. Thanks.
馬上就來了
They're on their way.
謝謝
Thank you.
汽車油箱蓋
你賣87年隨想曲汽車的油箱蓋嗎
You sell a gas cap ‭for an '87 Caprice wagon?
應該有
Should.
通用汽車的蓋子應該是底下藍色的
GM caps should be in the blue on the bottom there.
你確定不用我幫你
Now, you're sure I can't help you
把那些東西搬到車上去嗎  萬坎普太太
carry those to your car, Mrs. VanKamp?
別傻了
Don't be a silly. ‭
我只希望我沒占用你太多時間
I only hope I didn't take too much of your time
看我這些布滿灰塵的老照片
with all my dusty old photos.
當然沒有  你孫子的婚禮很精彩
‭Goodness, no. Your -- Your grandson's wedding was gorgeous.
我下次來
When I come back,
給你看我侄子的堅信禮
I'll show you ‭my niece's confirmation.
你要看看那些花
‭Wait'll you see the flowers!
玫瑰
Roses.
還有矮牽牛  蘭花
Petunias, orchids.
-花沒有味道  你知道嗎  -好吧
- They don't smell, you know? - ‭Well...
還有滿天星和矢車菊
And baby's breath and bachelor buttons.
-好啊  -鈴蘭
- Okay. - ‭Lilies of the valley.
等我看到我就信了
‭Well, I'll believe it when I see it.
雛菊  黛西都守口如瓶
Daisies -- Daisies don't tell.
出自上世紀20年代歌曲
那我可有得期待的了
Now I've got something to look forward to.
-行  拜拜  -拜
- Okay, bye-bye. - ‭Bye.
再見
See ya!
謝謝你們耐心的等待
Thank you for waiting so patiently.
下一個是誰
Who do we have next?
應該是我
That'd be me.
你好  你好
Hello, hello.
很高興再見到你
It's so good to see you again.
我護送你和你的委托人進入我的基地
I escorted you and your clients onto my base.
我熱情尊敬地對待你
I treated you ‭with hospitality and respect,
結果卻發現你嘴里吐出來的全是謊言
and now I come to find every word out of your mouth is a damn lie.
上尉  拜托  不如先坐下
Captain, please. Why don't -- sit down.
放輕松
Take a load off.
你需要免費的咖啡還是軟飲料
I'll get you a complimentary coffee or a soft drink?
還有你所謂的戰爭英雄  "軟糖"·塔爾博特
And your so-called war hero, "Fudge" Talbott?
沒這個人  根本沒有
No such person -- never was.
確實  里面進行了藝術性的虛構
Granted, some artistic license may have been taken.
你以欺詐的方式進入政府部門  先生
You entered government property under false pretenses, sir.
我不了解你們的流程
I am no expert on your procedures
還有那些章程什么的
and your protocols and whatnot,
所以如果我們遺漏了什么手續
so if -- if we failed to cross a "T" Or dot an "I,"
造成了誤會  我真誠地向你道歉
I sincerely apologize for any misunderstanding.
不不  這才不是誤會
N-No, no, no, it's not a misunderstanding!
別靠近啦  看看大局
Just step back! ‭B-Big picture this, okay?!
沒造成什么損壞吧
It -- ‭What damage was done?!
也沒人受傷吧
Hey, who was hurt, huh?
有什么影響嗎
What was damaged?
基地還在那里  對吧
The -- The base is still there, right?
那架B-52轟炸機應該還...
The B-52 is, I presume, still --
是B-29
B-29.
B-29轟炸機  菲菲是架B-29
B-29. FIFI's a B-29.
我不...
I don't...
你覺得這一切都只是個笑話吧
This is all just one big joke to you, huh?
你不喜歡那個廣告
You don't like the commercial.
我的確不喜歡
No, no, I don't,
但這件事跟廣告根本沒關...
but this has nothing to do with the comm--
我們隨時歡迎建設性的批評
Well, constructive criticism is always welcome.
-可我沒...  -但是你要知道
- But I didn't -- - But you should realize
大部分觀眾都覺得廣告振奮人心  甚至很愛國
that most people find it uplifting -- patriotic, even.
-不  -你去查查新兵招募人數
- No. ‭- You check ‭your recruiting numbers.
-我...  -你應該會發現有所增長  還有
- I-I-I -- - ‭I think you're gonna see an uptick, and you know what?
如果大家得知軟糖并沒有打過仗...
If it turns out that Fudge wasn't actually in the war --
根本沒有軟糖這個人  他當然沒打過仗
Fudge is not a person. He wasn't in the war.
湯姆·克魯斯也沒有
Well, neither was Tom Cruise,
但你瞧瞧《壯志凌云》對你的影響
and look what "Top Gun" did for you.
你欺騙了我  當著我的面說謊
You lied to me, you lied to my face,
我不能就這么放過你
and I can't let you get away with it.
那我們只能...
I-I think we just --
我們只能求同存異了
we're just gonna have to agree to disagree,
我給你倒杯咖啡帶走吧
so, uh, can I get you that coffee to go or...?
不  我來告訴你該怎么辦
No, no. I-I'm gonna tell you what's happening now.
你必須撤掉那個電視廣告
You're gonna take that ad off the air.
如果你在電視上再播放一次
And if you play that ad one more time,
我就告訴軍法檢察官
I'm gonna go to the Judge Advocate,
我們會逮捕你
and we will take you down --
非法闖入  虛假陳述
trespassing, false representation,
冒充戰爭英雄  所有這些罪名
stolen valor -- the whole nine yards.
不是吧  就因為廣告里那八秒鐘嗎
Seriously, for eight seconds of a TV commercial?
你撤掉那個廣告  否則就要付出慘痛的代價
You take that ad down, or there'll be hell to pay.
我說得夠清楚了嗎
That clear enough for you?
有本事就試試
Make me.
-真的嗎  -真的
- Yeah? ‭ - Yeah.
-試試  -我跟你斗到底
- Make you? - ‭Yeah, let's do this.
你把指揮官帶到這兒來
You bring ‭your commander down here,
我會向他解釋  是你帶我們進基地
and I'll explain to him how you let us on the base,
還給予我們明星般待遇
red-carpet treatment.
不  因為你騙了我
No, b-because you lied your way in.
我記憶中可不是這樣
Not how I remember it.
-事實就是...  -我有目擊證人給我作證
- What happened -- - And I've got witnesses to back me up.
你喜歡當空軍上尉嗎
Do you like being ‭an Air Force Captain, huh?
你覺得美國政府
You think the United States
會控告一個坐輪椅的老人嗎
wants to bring action against an old man in a wheelchair?!
在電視上他是站著的  他都沒坐在輪椅上
He was standing on TV. He wasn't even in a wheelchair!
沒錯  他那時的確是站著
Well, yeah. Well, periodically, he is.
但他出庭時
And when he shows up in court,
絕對會坐在輪椅上
you better believe he'll be in a wheelchair!
是啊  因為你就是發災難財的人渣
Right, because you're an ambulance-chasing piece of shit,
你們都一樣
'cause you're all the same --
-你跟其他律師都一樣  -總是這么道貌岸然
- you're the same as all the others. - Always on a high horse.
總是想讓我自己覺得...
Always trying to make me feel like I'm --
我是個律師
Look, um, I'm a lawyer,
這就是我每天的工作
and this is what I do all day, every day,
要不這樣吧
so h-how about this?
我不播有飛機的畫面
I-I won't fly jet planes --
你也不要告我們
you, uh, stay out of court.
你覺得怎么樣
Does that sound good?
你們這種人
You know, guys like you --
覺得自己很聰明
you think you're so damn smart,
不用跟其他人講道德
and you think you don't have to play straight with anybody.
風水輪流轉
The wheel is gonna turn.
你沒好果子吃的
It always does.
"你可以信賴的律師"
"A lawyer you can trust."
放狗屁
My ass!
感謝你為國服役
Thank you for your service!
半夜三點半  不是吧
3:30 in the morning? Seriously?
你能幫我弄到那個嗎
You get me that?
我不知道
I don't know.
-真的有這東西嗎  -是的
- It's a real thing? - ‭Yeah.
那可以  我認識一個人有門路
Then, yeah. ‭I know someone who can get it.
多少錢
How much?
我看起來像電商的人嗎
What do I look like -- RadioShack?
我付多少你給多少
It's gonna cost you whatever it costs me,
加上我的酬勞
plus my end.
先談談酬勞吧
Well, let's start with that.
一般是五百美元左右
Normally, be about $500,
但鑒于這是下班時間的上門服務
but seeing that this is an after-hours house call,
就一千吧
let's make it a grand.
小狗怎么樣
How's the pup?
還好嗎
Doing okay?
挺好的
Yeah.
它沒有被一個人留在家里一整天吧
She's not being left alone all day, is she?
-有人陪它  -那就好
- She's got plenty of company. ‭- Good.
這要花上我幾天時間
This is gonna take me a few days,
東西到手我會通知你
so I'll let you know.
下一次
And next time,
我們盡量在工作時間談工作
let's try to make business happen during business hours.
這一定對我周四要做的PPT有幫助
Well, this will certainly help my Thursday PowerPoint.
很好
Excellent.
這是凱文給亞利桑那州監管員的信的草稿
That's a draft letter from Kevin to the Arizona regulator.
我知道他喜歡溫情的筆觸
I know he likes the personal touch.
他一定會喜歡的
He's gonna love it.
我不敢相信你在三天內做了這么多
I can't believe you did all of this in three days.
我是不是看錯了
Am I reading this right --
你把重審提前了
did you get the rehearing moved up?
是的  那是三個可能的日期
Yeah. Those are three possible dates,
看你和凱文有沒有時間
pending your and Kevin's schedule.
我能安排最早的日期是四號
The soonest I could get is the 4th.
你把它提前了近三周
You moved it up almost three weeks.
我會再試試  看看能不能做得更好
I'll give it another shot and see if I can do better.
你是在開玩笑嗎
Are you kidding me? ‭
凱文會開心死了
Kevin'll be popping champagne!
我就知道你是最適合的人選
I knew ‭you were the right one for this.
梅薩維德銀行
我很感激你給我這次機會
Well, I appreciate the opportunity.
你應該聽聽那個傲慢的混蛋
Yeah, you should have heard how that arrogant jerk
在聽證會上是怎么跟我說的
spoke to me at the hearing.
就當著凱文的面
Right there, in front of Kevin,
他說我在添亂
he accuses me of muddying the waters --
添亂
muddying...the...waters.
他可是連地址都搞錯
I mean, he's the one who can't even get the address right.
是啊  那是...
Yeah, that's --
我知道你在哈姆林麥吉爾聯合律所有朋友
I know you have friends over at HHM,
他們肯定說得天花亂墜  可拜托
and they sure talk a good game, but come on.
像他們那樣的人  如果到了關鍵時刻
Guys like that, when crunch time comes,
一旦出了什么紕漏  就會讓別人背黑鍋
it's always someone else's fault.
佩奇
Paige?
很抱歉打擾了  快十一點三十了
I'm sorry to interrupt. It's almost 11:30.
謝謝  葛麗塔  我馬上就到
Thanks, Greta. I'll be right up.
我們周二的午飯還吃嗎
So, are we still on for lunch Tuesday?
當然
Absolutely.
還有佩奇  謝謝你做的一切
And, Paige, thank you... for everything.
不  謝謝你
No, thank you
收拾麥吉爾留下的爛攤子
for cleaning up that mess McGill left behind.
那個  你介不介意
Actually, would you mind
我明天一早再把它寄出去
if I messenger that over tomorrow morning, first thing?
我想在提交前最后看一下
I'd like to take one last look before we submit,
再檢查一下幾個地方
just double-check a few things.
沒問題  明天一早就寄
Sure. ‭So, tomorrow, first thing?
一定寄  謝謝
Absolutely. Thanks.
-回見  佩奇  -好  再見
- I'll see you, Paige. - ‭Okay, bye.
進展怎么樣了
How's it coming in there?
挺好的
Good!
-我不是想催你  -不  沒事的
- Don't mean to rush ya. - No, it's okay.
我好了
I'm done.
半條彩虹
Half a rainbow?
難道你不想做完再走嗎
Don't you want to keep going till you do the whole thing?
不  如果你做完了  我就做完了
No. If you're done, I'm done.
你的委托人好像很喜歡那條彩虹
You know, your clients seem to like that rainbow.
他們會想念它嗎
‭Think they're gonna miss it?
等他們看到新的圖案
Wait till they see what's going up next.
他們會喜歡的  你會喜歡的
They're gonna love it. You're gonna love it.
我需要擔心嗎
Yeah? Should I be worried?
不用
Nope.
我們離開這里怎么樣
Whaddya say ‭we get the hell outta here?
好啊
Sounds good.
你準備好走了嗎
You ready ta hit it?
抱歉  我就再檢查一個地方
Sorry. I just need to check one thing.
最多兩分鐘
It'll be two minutes, tops.
冰
歐內斯托
Ernesto.
早安  麥吉爾先生
Morning, Mr. McGill.
他們店里沒賣富士蘋果
They didn't have Fuji apples,
所以我給你買了蜜糖脆蘋果
so I got you Honeycrisp.
-希望你不會介意  -這種蘋果也行
- Hope that's all right. - I'm sure it'll be fine.
你有去拿...
Did you get the, uh...
我去拿了
Yeah. I got them.
我買了之后
I went ahead and, um,
想著是否要...
I figured I should maybe...
我已經包好了  安全起見
I wrapped them up, you know, for safety.
你可真體貼
That's very thoughtful of you,
但我現在就要用  你可以...
but I need them now, so, if you...
-你確定沒問題嗎  -沒問題
- You sure it's okay? ‭- It's okay.
沒錯
Yeap.
很好
Perfect.
該死
Shit!
歐內斯托  你能過來一下嗎
Ernesto, ‭could you come in here, please?
還是沒法自己動手
Thought I could do this myself.
你能幫我換一下電池嗎
Would you mind, uh, changing the batteries?
沒問題  麥吉爾先生
Sure thing, Mr. McGill.
好
Yeah.
謝謝
Thanks.
我把1261改成了1216
‭I changed 1261 to 1216.
-是我干的  -關掉
- It was me. - ‭Turn that off!
-快關掉  -事情的經過就...
- Turn it off! ‭- It all went down exactly...
關掉它
Turn it off!
你什么都沒聽到
You did not hear that!
好了
All right.
是這樣的  歐內斯托
Okay, Ernesto...
剛剛是我不對  你做得沒錯
that's my fault, not yours.
既然你都聽到了
But now that you've heard it,
那有些事希望你明白
you need to understand something.
你明白保密有多重要吧
You know ‭about confidentiality, right?
作為哈姆林麥吉爾聯合律所的員工
As employees ‭of Hamlin Hamlin&McGill,
你我都受客戶保密限制的約束
you and I are both bound by the strictures of client confidentiality,
受法律約束  我們都一樣
by law, both of us, by law.
你懂我的意思嗎
You understand what I'm saying?
所以我不能把這件事告訴任何人
So I'm not supposed to tell anyone?
沒錯  誰都不行
That's right, no matter who,
出于什么理由都不行
no matter what reasons you think you might have,
你不能  絕對不能告訴任何人
you must not , you cannot tell anyone.
否則會產生很嚴重的后果
There could be terrible consequences --
能影響你下半生的后果
life-changing consequences.
我們也不希望你陷入麻煩之中
And we don't want you to get into trouble.
如果你因為這件事受到了牽連
If something were to happen to you because of this,
我會很不好受的
I'd feel sick about it.
好了  我說完了
Okay. Enough said.
我想
I guess...
我還是去繼續放雜貨吧
I'll go finish ‭puttin' away the groceries.
可以嗎
Okay?
謝謝你  歐內斯托
Thank you, Ernesto.
射頻信標追蹤儀
使用說明書
距離目標  兩米
無信號
距離目標
周二天氣預報
Highs for Tuesday,
最高溫十八度左右
high temperatures will be in the mid-60s
風速為每小時五英里至十英里
with 5 to 10-mile-per-hour winds,
晚間則可能伴有零星陣雨
but expect scattered showers Tuesday night
最低溫維持在五度左右
with lows in the 40s.
周三多云
Wednesday will be partly cloudy
最高溫達十三度
with high temperatures in the mid-50s.
格蘭茨的氣溫在八度左右
The Grants area will have temperatures in the mid-40s,
并伴有時速為十五至二十英里的西南風
with southwest winds 15 to 20 miles per hour.
現在讓我們回到您最喜愛的《老歌金曲》
Now let's get back to more of your favorite "Sound Souvenir Oldies"
史蒂夫·里基茨將在KDSK繼續為您主持
with "The Steve Ricketts Program" on KDSK, 92.7 FM.
謝謝你  德里克  過幾天的天氣真好  就跟...
Thank you, Derek. Love those temperatures, it's almost like...
*過去記憶刺痛心弦*
*Taunting me a memory*
*如一曲哀樂繞心頭*
*Like a haunting melody*
*過去記憶  渴望解脫*
*Memory, wanting always to be free*
*我是否一無所有*
*Is there nothing left for me*
距離目標